Guide to the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Photographs PHOTOS 097
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Prints
  - Addendum 1
    - Scholarships, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Scholarship Winners, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Shop Committee Meetings (Box 15)
    - Softball, 1996 (Box 15)
    - TWA Flight 800 (Box 15)
    - Walkathon, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Yale Club (Box 15)
    - Election (Box 15)
    - JAL (Box 15)
  - Addendum 2, 1938-1974
    - Two Photograph Albums, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Assorted Photographs, 1938-1963 (Box 14)
    - Panoramic Photographs - Banquets and Conventions, 1949, 1955 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 14)
- Negatives, circa 1984-1999
  - Negatives (Box 21)
  - Negatives (Box 21)
  - Hotel Voice negatives, shoot number 52864, circa 1988 - 1999 (Box 21)
- Unprocessed (Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20)